hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jared
microkowski on this podcast we're going
to talk about ways for you to grow your
coaching business and get more clients
and today I want to talk about how to
grow your coaching business with paid
advertising now I understand a lot of
people have concerns about running paid
ads they think well what if it doesn't
produce results what if I don't make
enough money the truth is there's a risk
in everything there's always risk so
first off you have to accept that risk
and realize you don't always have
control over the outcomes of how things
go but if you follow the system that I
teach you if you follow my trainings if
you follow what's on this podcast you're
gonna get a lot closer to your goals
than most people are and so what I'm
going to help you do is I'm going to
help you map out our formula that we use
for running paid ads it's going to be
incredible for you also we're hosting a
live event we're actually hosting two
live events coming up this week one on
Tuesday all about growing your email
list step by step and one on Saturday
all about getting coaching clients
through paid advertising so be sure to
check those out as well the event is
tomorrow and then on Saturday so that's
gonna be awesome
here's the first thing
running paid ads it's not like it used
to be it's not like the process used to
be
now everything has changed the whole
landscape when it comes to running your
paid advertising has changed towards the
direction of the tick tockification of
the internet to where Tick Tock has
influenced how we interact how we talk
how we communicate and how we connect
with people
and so you have to make your paid ads we
use video ads first off video ads
convert way better than graphic ads do
and so we have we recommend that you
build out video ads where you record
yourself with a cell phone use an app
like captions dot AI write that down
captions dot AI to put the captions on
the screen and then you run those videos
off your cell phone as video ads that's
what converts the best okay you want to
keep it short and sweet engaging and
speaking directly to who your target
client is now here's the controversial
part of this and a big part of our
process for building coaching businesses
is you want to repel
you want to exclude you want to even go
as far as to
um alienate from your messaging
I know that sounds harsh but
make it to where the people that are not
a good fit for your coaching program
will never even see your ad
because you're not trying to persuade
them to work with you that you get so
clear on who you can get results for the
most that you make your ads speak to
those people
the biggest reason why most people lose
money with paid advertising
is because they have a crappy offer and
their offer is disconnected from what
people actually want in the marketplace
and so if you're a coach if you're a
trainer if you're a mentor and you're
trying to run ads and you're like I'm
going to run ads to this off to this
program and people are going to love it
and you lose money that's the problem
that most people have as they're trying
to force a square peg into a round hole
they're trying to force people to like
something they have no interest in
because the coach or the mentor thinks
people would benefit from this and I get
it I want to honor you of course you got
a great message it's going to help
people but if people don't connect with
your message in a way that fits them
meaning
the way that you might describe how you
help your clients
how you would describe the
transformation you bring your clients
may not be how they would actually
describe it if they were talking to a
friend about the problems they're having
and the struggle that they're dealing
with and so that's the biggest
disconnect with most coaches and mentors
is they lead with what they think people
need not with the exact words that
people want and the desires that people
want even if those desires aren't
healthy for them even if those desires
are not what's going to get them the
result and see that's one of the biggest
things is that some coaches and mentors
believe that that's unethical to lead
with what people want even if it's not
going to help them
it's actually how you make a whole lot
of money you give people what they need
but you lead with what they want you
bottle up the moment
that the light bulb goes off in your
target client
and that's how you make the sale
and we do that with virtual events on
Zoom where people sign up for events to
listen to a training and then we sell
them on our program we build trust with
them around the training and we sell
them on our programs that's how we've
made six hundred thousand dollars in the
last seven months in our coaching
business
when I walk people through the process
start to finish doing this and that's
what I Mentor people on that's what I
help you with on this podcast I want to
help you with my content that's what I
help you with my brand is dedicated to
helping coaches trainers and mentors
make a crap ton of money with their
business more money than they know what
to do with and make way more impact than
they ever could before you know if you
made 10 million dollars in your coaching
business the amount of impact that you
would be having would be so much greater
than you could ever imagine and that's
what I help coaches and mentors do but
it starts with knowing how to actually
get the attention of your the right
Prospect how do you get the attention of
the person
who is going to benefit the most
from your training how do you show up in
front of the person who's going to spend
money with you and get the most results
that's going to make you rich
because you're gonna have so many case
studies coming in of people succeeding
like we just got in from one of our
clients Duke he made over fifteen
thousand dollars spending 600 in
Facebook ads following this system
following our trainings following our
process
the problem is most coaches and mentors
are leading with what they want
and not with what the target client
wants now how do you discover what the
target client wants
the feedback loop you use the feedback
loop and this is a million dollar piece
of advice that if you listen to this
it'll change your business
here's the funny thing though I've
worked with I've worked with thousands
of coaches
most like 90
8 percent
of the coaches that I've worked with
because and I'm talking even the ones
that are in my coaching group maybe
eighty percent of the ones that are in
my coaching group but 98 of most people
I say this all the time and they they
they gloss over this one thing that I'm
about to tell you they ignore it
and and and you are probably going to
ignore what I'm about to tell you
until
you know the old saying is that this
when the student is ready the teacher
arrives okay and so you might not be
ready to hear what I'm about to tell you
that will make you a million plus if you
apply it in your business
and you're like get up get out with it
already what is it right
patience Padawan that's Obi-Wan Kenobi
would say
I've been watching the Star Wars Clone
Wars series a lot lately so what is it
the feedback loop
you create a mechanism in your funnel
where you survey people and they tell
you what it is that they're struggling
with and what they want to learn and you
ask questions that benefit you and only
you
because you're going to then take that
data
and we filter it into chat GPT
and then chat gbt spits out
how to sell to them
what are their pain points what are
their struggles
what are their biggest issues that
they're dealing with
that's how we come up with our offers
that's how we make the kind of money
that we make that's how our clients make
the kind of money that they make
but most people ignore the feedback loop
they ignore the very thing that's
actually going to make them
the kind of money that they want to make
they ignore
the very process
that's going to produce a result in
their business and they complain that
they're struggling to get clients they
complain that they don't have enough
time for ineffective advertising
campaigns they complain that it's
difficult to grow a coaching business
they complain that nobody gives good
training out there
they're worried that their business
isn't going to succeed and they they
stress that they don't have a clear
marketing plan I'm telling you
the feedback loop is literally it
the feedback loop is the strategy
that in everything that I teach is the
most important
because when you could attract the
people that are qualified for your
coaching and you get them to tell you
what are they struggling with what do
they want to learn
how can you help them
and you and you you do so without
judgment
without shaming people
without people feeling like it's not
safe to tell you these things because
that's the thing A lot of people are
embarrassed to tell you what they're
dealing with they're embarrassed to tell
you what they're going through and
they're embarrassed to verbalize why
they struggle
they want to learn a proven method but
they're not willing to to do what it
takes because they don't want to come
face to face with the truth that they
don't actually understand their client
they don't even understand what their
client wants and what's cool is we have
mechanisms now where you can use
artificial intelligence to actually tell
you a lot of this data which is super
awesome and so we take the AI
it's very accurate we build campaigns
around it and we test our assumption we
use the scientific experimentation
method to put out their offers that
people want
and then we have the feedback loop again
we we prove our test by having another
round of the feedback loop where people
tell us what do they want and it dials
deeper and deeper and deeper and then
more you dial down doing that the more
money you're going to make with your
paid ads and the lower your cost is
going to be
by listening to your target client by
listening to what they want by listening
to what their desires are
and then what you want to do is you want
to take a look at okay who bought from
me what was that moment in time where
they had the epiphany
where just the light bulb went off where
they trusted
what we're teaching
where they decided okay I need to take
action on this and they purchased from
you and so when you can find that moment
and you can find as many people as
possible that are at that moment and you
walk them through a process of growing
and trust with you
you walk them through a process of
believing because they have to believe
it before they even do it if they don't
believe that they can do what you're
going to coach on they won't buy from
you
I can't get a single client if the
people that I talk to don't believe that
they can actually do the thing I'm
selling
and so I have to impart
Faith to people first off how do you do
that with your enthusiasm
the definition of enthusiasm is to show
intense enjoyment interest and approval
to where you have this fervor this Zeal
this excitement
the word was originally used to refer to
somebody who was possessed by God
which is very interesting and and but
that's what it is there's a power behind
enthusiasm you could hear me right now
in my voice I have enthusiasm a lot of
coaches I see out there they're they're
in the doldrums they're in the the the
pit they're they're in the struggle
and they're trying to convince people
that they should work with them instead
of demonstrating a dream life for their
clients you want to know how you attract
clients demonstrate a dream life to them
demonstrate straight their dreams back
to them
and you'll get more people than you ever
could imagine when you run paid ad
campaigns that literally demonstrate
your clients dreams right back to them
and that's how you make money
and that's what we walk you through and
that's what we show you how to do it all
starts with the offer and it all starts
with
what does the Target client want by
using the feedback loop
you can get more clarity on how to get
more clients in your business
okay and so listen if you if you if you
see one of the live events that we're
running register for it if you're a
coach if you're a trainer if you're a
mentor I can't point you to like sign up
for this event this day because like
once it's done it's done but I I do them
every month okay and so go to my website
jeremicorkowski.com find one of the live
events that I'm doing register for it
and start to get results in your
coaching business start to make the kind
of money that you know as possible
twenty thousand thirty thousand forty
thousand dollars a month in your
business
let's go for it my friends we'll talk
soon have a good one